{
    "id": "f10baa6901424d6587c36446a650ed51",
    "title": "Sentence Completion Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "To hit a person when he is down is a contemptuous thing to ................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "be done",
                "done"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "In 1665, a great epidemic ............................................. the death of 63,000 people in London.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "caused",
                "has caused",
                "had caused"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "..................................... his lack of interest in the affairs of the society, the members decided to depose him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Because",
                "Because of",
                "Despite"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy ...................................... thousands of foreign stamps since",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has collected",
                "is collecting",
                "collected"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We watched the airplane until it disappeared ....................................... the clouds.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "by",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "According to activists, action ......................................... long ago to preserve forests.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "must take",
                "must be taken",
                "must have been taken"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "When Sophia said that she was coming to see me I wondered what .......................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "the problem was",
                "was the problem"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The doctor suggested that I .......................................... walk on and try to get help while he stayed with the injured person.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Jack told his sister that he .......................................... her help in solving the problem.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wants",
                "wanted"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The judge paid no attention ......................................... the boy was unhappy at home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "to the fact that"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}